https://www.community1st.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyWCDev2018-10-30T10:32:59-07:00
Download our full Privacy Policy via PDF.What Does Community First Bank Do with your personal information?Why do financial companies collect personal information?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information.  Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing.  Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share and protect your personal information.  Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What we share:The types of personal information we collect and share depends on the product or service you have with us.  This information can include:
Social Security number
Account balances
Credit history
Transaction history
Overdraft history
Wire transfer instructions
When you are no longer our client, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How is your information shared?All financial companies need to share their clients’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their clients’ personal information; the reasons Community First Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does Community First Bank share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes –
Such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigation, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes – To offer our products and services to you
Yes
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
No
We don’t share
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – Information about your transactions and experiences
Yes
No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes – Information about your creditworthiness
Yes
No
For affiliates’ to market to you
Yes
No
For non-affiliates to market to you
No
We don’t share
Please do not hesitate to call our main branch with any questions you may have: (509) 735-3435
Contact Us
INTERNET BANKING
PH: (509) 783-0955
TELEPHONE BANKING
PH: (866) 783-3015
HOME LOAN TEAM
PH: (509) 783-4005
COMMERCIAL LENDING
Full Name*Email*
PhoneMessage*Your security is important to us, although this site is encrypted, for your safety please do not include personal information such as your address or account number in the message box above.LocationKennewickRichlandPascoConnellGrandridgeServiceBusiness BankingCommercial loansPersonal BankingPersonal loansHome LoansCAPTCHAEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Contact Our Mortgage Team
Office: (509) 783-4005
Fax: (509) 579-0327
EMAIL: homeloans@community1st.com
Jamin Clark, Vice President and Mortgage Department Manager (NMLS #418805)
jclark@community1st.com
O: (509)820-4003 C: (509)948-2935
Derek Robinson, Vice President and Mortgage Consultant (NMLS #1616459)
drobinson@community1st.com
O: (509)820-4008 C: (303) 888-8654
Dora Castaneda, Vice President and Mortgage Consultant (NMLS #1616459)
dcastaneda@community1st.com
O: (509)820.4013 C: (509)845.9787
Sandy Loosveldt, Mortgage Processor (NMLS #1560730)
sloosveldt@community1st.com
(509) 820-4006
Julie Rogers, Mortgage Processor (NMLS #404183)
jrogers@community1st.com
(509) 820-4004
Melissa Ulmen, Mortgage Processor (NMLS #1597557)
mulmen@community1st.com
(509) 735-5017
Send us a message
Full Name*Email*
PhoneMessage*Your security is important to us, although this site is encrypted, for your safety please do not include personal information such as your address or account number in the message box above.LocationKennewickRichlandPascoConnellGrandridgeCAPTCHANameThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
Go to Top
